{
    "id": "7da1286073024b1aba3ea9d94250bdac",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The moderator maintained an ……………………………… manner throughout the furious debate.",
            "description": "Impassive can mean calm or cool.",
            "answers": [
                "impassive",
                "impassioned",
                "impassionate"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The class was ………………………….. for the vacation to begin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "impatient",
                "unpatient",
                "inpatient"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Try to remain ……………………………….. until you have heard both sides of the story.",
            "description": "Impartial is the correct word.",
            "answers": [
                "unpartial",
                "impartial",
                "dispartial"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The leader roused the protestors with an ………………………………….. speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "impassive",
                "impassioned",
                "passioned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her parents …………………………… of her going to dances alone.",
            "description": "Disapprove is the correct word. Disapprove means object to.",
            "answers": [
                "disapprove",
                "unapprove",
                "inapprove"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………….. from the stitches was not too great.",
            "description": "Discomfort means ache or pain.",
            "answers": [
                "uncomfort",
                "discomfort",
                "incomfort"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The plot was too ………………………………. to make sense.",
            "description": "Disconnected means confused or illogical.",
            "answers": [
                "unconnected",
                "ill-connected",
                "disconnected"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Her character is …………………………….",
            "description": "Impeccable means flawless. ",
            "answers": [
                "unpeccable",
                "impeccable",
                "inpeccable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………………. with her dull life.",
            "description": "Discontented means unhappy. ",
            "answers": [
                "uncontented",
                "discontented",
                "miscontented"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dense hedge of thorns formed an …………………………………. barrier around the castle.",
            "description": "Impenetrable means impassable.",
            "answers": [
                "inpenetrable",
                "dispenetrable",
                "impenetrable"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. his good name with ugly gossip.",
            "description": "To discredit is to defame.",
            "answers": [
                "uncredited",
                "discredited",
                "miscredited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The difference between the two colors is ………………………………",
            "description": "Imperceptible means unnoticeable. ",
            "answers": [
                "imperceptible",
                "unperceptible",
                "disperceptible"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}